Well, last pastor called, could my as a psych or codcap, but turned to you in case you're not.
Let us pray in the name of the most holy Trinity, and name the Father, and of the Son, and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
We celebrate Almighty God that 125 years ago, the city of Miami was founded and is grown.
We gave you thanks for your blessings throughout the past century and a quarter upon our community.
May we honor you, the leadership, and all of this community citizens, residents, and visitors,
by the manner in which we implore individual and combine reliance on you.
As we apply our intelligence, skills, and gifts for the betterment of all, when counted as in this meanness appality.
As the season changes from winter to spring, we also change so that continued growth occur.
And we hand over a rich past, the future generations.
Jesus Christ invites us to join him, making all things new.
May we accept this invitation as we build on our past and pray and work seeking to promote a bright future.
God, the Father, pour out the Holy Spirit upon us, so that we may be effective disciples of Jesus Christ, our Lord.
Amen.
Thank you.
I want to leave you from the future.
Our pledge allegiance to the Father of the United States of America, and to the Republic, for which it stands, one nation under God, individual, liberty and justice for all.
Thank you, Father.
I then pour out public input.
It's anybody in my audience.
Coach could go to the trust.
On five staff is recommended.
I have them six and seven, and they can send it to them.
We have a motion if nobody has any objections.
I'll make a motion.
Now, second motion.
Forster.
All right, Western.
All right.
Johnson.
May I do a new business thing?
Done.
Staff reports.
You guys have any?
Then you'll ask.
It's not because time.
But I trust you.
Me and the hospital.
You guys have nothing?
No.
Journal.
Mr. Jones.
Second.
Western.
Aye.
Forster.